13ideas.com 2008-06-16

# 13 Ideas » Privacy Policy

### Your Privacy

13 Ideas, LLC understand and share your concern about how personal information is collected, used and shared. As such, our procedures are designed to ensure that you are protected under United States privacy laws.

When using this website (site) or by registering with us, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, but only in accordance with this Privacy Policy which directs that such information is handled sensitively and securely.

### Personal Information Collected

We collect personal information when you send us emails, submit queries to us or subscribe to one of the services offered through our site. The information we collect generally includes your name, telephone number, address and email address. Your personal information is used to respond to your queries or requests for service from our office. If you do not give us personal information, we may be unable to respond to your query or provide the requested service.

### Protection of Personal Information

In accordance with the Act, your personal information will not be disclosed to a third party other than in the circumstances where it is necessary for law enforcement purposes, where we believe there is a threat to a person’s safety or health or where we have told you this will occur before obtaining the information.

Our site from time to time may also contain links to other sites. As we do not govern those sites, you should check the privacy policy for each linked site.

### Access to your Information

You may access the personal information we hold about you in accordance with the Act. You may also ask us to amend any of your personal information which you believe is inaccurate or incorrect. We will comply with the Act regarding correction of personal information.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time, so you may like to check it each time you visit the site.

### Disclaimer

While all reasonable care has been taken in the preparation of the material contained in this website (site), 13 Ideas accepts no responsibility and disclaim all liability with respect to the currency, accuracy, completeness or adequacy of the information in this site. You are encouraged to make your own enquiries to verify the information contained within the site, before entering into any transaction on the basis of the information provided on this site.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions or comments related to privacy, please contact us.
